Finding Aid for Alexander G. Ruthven Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- President's Office, 1929-1952
  - Correspondence Files, 1929-1951
    - 1938-1939
      - Football (Box 22)
        (22-13)
      - Fr-Fz (Box 22)
        (22-14)
      - Fraternities (Box 22)
        (22-15)
      - Furstenberg, Albert C. (Box 22)
        (22-16)
      - Ga-Go (Box 22)
        (22-17)
      - Gp-Gz (Box 22)
        (22-18)
      - Griffin, Clare E. (Box 22)
        (22-19)
      - Ha-Kd (Box 22)
        (22-20)
      - Haynes, Harley A. (Box 22)
        (22-21)
      - He-Hi (Box 22)
        (22-22)
      - Hj-Hz (Box 22)
        (22-23)
      - I (Box 22)
        (22-24)
      - J (Box 22)
        (22-25)
      - K (Box 22)
        (22-26)
      - La-Lh (Box 22)
        (22-27)
      - Latin-American Relations (Box 22)
        (22-28)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 22)
        (22-29)
      - Li-Lz (Box 22)
        (22-30)
      - Ma-Mb (Box 22)
        (22-31)
      - Mc-Mh (Box 22)
        (22-32)
      - Memberships (Ruthven) (Box 22)
        (22-33)
      - Mi-Mt (Box 22)
        (22-34)
      - Michigan (Box 22)
        (22-35)
      - Murphy, Frank (Box 22)
        (22-36)
      - Mu-Mz (Box 23)
        (23-1)
      - Museum (Box 23)
        (23-2)
      - Na-Nn (Box 23)
        (23-3)
      - National Association of State Universities (Box 23)
        (23-4)
      - National (Box 23)
        (23-5)
      - Nelson, J. Raleigh (Box 23)
        (23-6)
      - New York World's Fair (Box 23)
        (23-7)
      - No-Nz (Box 23)
        (23-8)
      - North Central Association (Box 23)
        (23-9)
      - O (Box 23)
        (23-10)
      - Pa (Box 23)
        (23-11)
      - Pb-Pz (Box 23)
        (23-12)
      - Physical Education (Board in Control) (Box 23)
        (23-13)
      - Q (Box 23)
        (23-14)
      - Questionnaires (Box 23)
        (23-15)
      - Ra-Re (Box 23)
        (23-16)
      - Regional Research Laboratory (Box 23)
        (23-17)
      - Rf-Rz (Box 23)
        (23-18)
      - Riegel, John W. (Box 23)
        (23-19)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 23)
        (23-20)
      - Sa-Sh (Box 23)
        (23-21)
      - Scholarships, Prizes, etc. (Box 23)
        (23-22)
      - Seals, Pins, Memos, etc. (Box 23)
        (23-23)
      - Shields, Edmand C. (Box 23)
        (23-24)
      - Si-Sp (Box 23)
        (23-25)
      - Sink, Charles A. (Box 23)
        (23-26)
      - Smith, Ira M. (Box 23)
        (23-27)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 23)
        (23-28)
      - Sq-Sz (Box 23)
        (23-29)
      - Stason, E. Blythe (Box 23)
        (23-30)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 23)
        (23-31)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 23)
        (23-32)
      - Traffic Control (Box 23)
        (23-33)
      - U (Box 24)
        (24-1)
      - United States Legislature (Box 24)
        (24-2)
      - V (Box 24)
        (24-3)
      - Wa-Wh (Box 24)
        (24-4)
      - Wi-Wz (Box 24)
        (24-5)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 24)
        (24-6)
    - 1939-1940
      - Aa-Am (Box 24)
        (24-7)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 24)
        (24-8)
      - Advertising (Box 24)
        (24-9)
      - Alumni Association (Box 24)
        (24-10)
      - Alumni Relations (Box 24)
        (24-11)
      - American (Box 24)
        (24-12)
      - American Council on Education (Box 24)
        (24-13)
      - An-Az (Box 24)
        (24-14)
      - Anderson, Henry C. (Box 24)
        (24-15)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 24)
        (24-16)
      - Associations, Groups, etc. (Meetings of) (Box 24)
        (24-17)
      - Associations, Institutes, Bureaus, etc. (Box 24)
        (24-18)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 24)
        (24-19)
      - Ba-Bd (Box 24)
        (24-20)
      - Barbour Scholarship Committee (Box 24)
        (24-21)
      - Be-Bn (Box 24)
        (24-22)
      - Bishop, William W. (Box 24)
        (24-23)
      - Blakeman, Edward W. (Box 24)
        (24-24)
      - Bo-Bz (Box 24)
        (24-25)
      - Ca-Cd (Box 24)
        (24-26)
      - Cancer Research (Institution for) (Box 24)
        (24-27)
      - Ce-Ck (Box 24)
        (24-28)
      - Cl-Co (Box 24)
        (24-29)
      - Clements Library (Box 25)
        (25-1)
      - Commencement (1940) (Box 25)
        (25-2)
      - Cooley Foundation (Box 25)
        (25-3)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 25)
        (25-4)
      - Crawford, Ivan C. (Box 25)
        (25-5)
      - Crowley, David H. (Box 25)
        (25-6)
      - Da (Box 25)
        (25-7)
      - Db-Di (Box 25)
        (25-8)
      - Dj-Dz (Box 25)
        (25-9)
      - Dormitories (Box 25)
        (25-10)
      - Dormitories (Naming) (Box 25)
        (25-11)
      - Ea-Em (Box 25)
        (25-12)
      - Elliott, Eugene B. (Box 25)
        (25-13)
      - En-Ez (Box 25)
        (25-14)
      - Extension Service (Box 25)
        (25-15)
      - Fa-Fq (Box 25)
        (25-16)
      - Fees (Committee on) (Box 25)
        (25-17)
      - Fr-Fz (Box 25)
        (25-18)
      - Ga-Gn (Box 25)
        (25-19)
      - Go-Gz (Box 25)
        (25-20)
      - Gram, Lewis M. (Box 25)
        (25-21)
      - Griffin, Clare E. (Box 25)
        (25-22)
      - Ha-Hd (Box 25)
        (25-23)
      - Haynes, Harley A. (Box 25)
        (25-24)
      - He-Hi (Box 25)
        (25-25)
      - Hj-Hz (Box 25)
        (25-26)
      - I (Box 25)
        (25-27)
      - J (Box 25)
        (25-28)
      - Ka-Kg (Box 25)
        (25-29)
      - Kh-Kz (Box 25)
        (25-30)
      - La-Lh (Box 25)
        (25-31)
      - Latin-American Relations (Box 25)
        (25-32)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 25)
        (25-33)
      - Lecturers (Box 25)
        (25-34)
      - Li-Lz (Box 25)
        (25-35)
      - Ma-Md (Box 25)
        (25-36)
      - Me-Mo (Box 25)
        (25-37)
      - Medical School (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
        (25-38)
      - Memberships (Box 25)
        (25-39)
      - Michigan (Box 26)
        (26-1)
      - Mp-Mz (Box 26)
        (26-2)
      - Na-Nz (Box 26)
        (26-3)
      - National, etc. (Box 26)
        (26-4)
      - National Association of State Universities (Box 26)
        (26-5)
      - National Youth Administration (Box 26)
        (26-6)
      - Nelson, J. Raleigh (Box 26)
        (26-7)
      - Nursing (School of) (Box 26)
        (26-8)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 26)
        (26-9)
      - Obenauer (The American Synergies) (Box 26)
        (26-10)
      - Pa-Pe (Box 26)
        (26-11)
      - Pf-Pz (Box 26)
        (26-12)
      - Physical Education (Board in Control) (Box 26)
        (26-13)
      - Qa-Qz (Box 26)
        (26-14)
      - Questionnaires (Box 26)
        (26-15)
      - Ra-Ri (Box 26)
        (26-16)
      - Refugee Material (Box 26)
        (26-17)
      - Rj-Rz (Box 26)
        (26-18)
      - Sa-Sh (Box 26)
        (26-19)
      - Scholarships, Fellowships, Prizes, etc. (Box 26)
        (26-20)
      - Si-Sz (Box 26)
        (26-21)
      - Sink, Charles A. (Box 26)
        (26-22)
      - Smith (Miscellaneous) (Box 26)
        (26-23)
      - Smith, Ira, M. (Box 26)
        (26-24)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 26)
        (26-25)
      - Stason, E. Blythe (Box 26)
        (26-26)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 26)
        (26-27)
      - Student Religious Association (Box 26)
        (26-28)
      - T (Box 26)
        (26-29)
      - Ua-Uz (Box 26)
        (26-30)
      - U.S. Government Departments (Box 26)
        (26-31)
      - U.S. Legislature (Box 26)
        (26-32)
      - V (Box 26)
        (26-33)
      - Wa-Wh (Box 26)
        (26-34)
      - Wi-Wz (Box 26)
        (26-35)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 26)
        (26-36)
      - Yoakum C.S. (Box 26)
        (26-37)
    - 1940-1941
      - Aa-Ak (Box 27)
        (27-1)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 27)
        (27-2)
      - Al-Az (Box 27)
        (27-3)
      - Alumni Association (Box 27)
        (27-4)
      - Alumni Relations (Box 27)
        (27-5)
      - American (Box 27)
        (27-6)
      - American Council on Education (Box 27)
        (27-7)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 27)
        (27-8)
      - A.A.U. (Topics for Meeting), 1940 (Box 27)
        (27-9)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 27)
        (27-10)
      - Associations, Institutes, Bureaus, etc. (Box 27)
        (27-11)
      - Ba-Be (Box 27)
        (27-12)
      - Barbour Scholarship Committee (Box 27)
        (27-13)
      - Bf-Bt (Box 27)
        (27-14)
      - Bishop, William W. (Box 27)
        (27-15)
      - Blakeman, Edward W. (Box 27)
        (27-16)
      - Bu-Bz (Box 27)
        (27-17)
      - Ca-Ck (Box 27)
        (27-18)
      - Carr, L.J. (Box 27)
        (27-19)
      - Cl-Co (Box 27)
        (27-20)
      - Clements Library (Box 27)
        (27-21)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 27)
        (27-22)
      - Da-Di (Box 27)
        (27-23)
      - Director of Residence Halls (Report of) (Box 27)
        (27-24)
      - Dj-Dz (Box 27)
        (27-25)
      - Dormitories (Box 27)
        (27-26)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 28)
        (28-1)
      - Edmonson, J.B. (Box 28)
        (28-2)
      - Engineering Alumni Reunion (Box 28)
        (28-3)
      - Evaluation of Faculty Services (Box 28)
        (28-4)
      - Fa-Fk (Box 28)
        (28-5)
      - Fern, George H. (Box 28)
        (28-6)
      - Fl-Fq (Box 28)
        (28-7)
      - Fr-Fz (Box 28)
        (28-8)
      - Furstenberg, Albert C. (Box 28)
        (28-9)
      - Ga-Gq (Box 28)
        (28-10)
      - Gr-Gz (Box 28)
        (28-11)
      - Gram, Levis M. (Box 28)
        (28-12)
      - Griffith, Effie M. (Box 28)
        (28-13)
      - Ha-Hd (Box 28)
        (28-14)
      - Haynes, Harley A. (Box 28)
        (28-15)
      - He-Hz (Box 28)
        (28-16)
      - Henderson, Mary B. (House) (Box 28)
        (28-17)
      - I (Box 28)
        (28-18)
      - J (Box 28)
        (28-19)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 28)
        (28-20)
      - Kellogg Foundation (Box 28)
        (28-21)
      - Kraus, Edward H (Box 28)
        (28-22)
      - La-Lb (Box 28)
        (28-23)
      - Latin-American Materials (Box 28)
        (28-24)
      - Lc-Lz (Box 28)
        (28-25)
      - Librarianship, Material (Box 28)
        (28-26)
      - Library Storage (Box 28)
        (28-27)
      - Lynch, John D (Box 28)
        (28-28)
      - Ma-Md (Box 28)
        (28-29)
      - Me-Mi (Box 28)
        (28-30)
      - Memberships, Committees, etc. (Box 28)
        (28-31)
      - Michigan (Box 29)
        (29-1)
      - Michigan Daily (Box 29)
        (29-2)
      - Mj-Mz (Box 29)
        (29-3)
      - Moore, Earl V. (Box 29)
        (29-4)
      - Na-Nz (Box 29)
        (29-5)
      - National, etc. (Box 29)
        (29-6)
      - National Association of State Universities (Box 29)
        (29-7)
      - Naval R.O.T.C. (Box 29)
        (29-8)
      - Nelson, J. Raleigh (Box 29)
        (29-9)
      - New Education Fellowship Conference (Box 29)
        (29-10)
      - N.Y. Alumni Talk (1941) (Box 29)
        (29-11)
      - O (Box 29)
        (29-12)
      - Pa-Ph (Box 29)
        (29-13)
      - Pi-Pz (Box 29)
        (29-14)
      - Physical Education (Board in Control of) (Box 29)
        (29-15)
      - Public Health (Box 29)
        (29-16)
      - Qa-Qz (Box 29)
        (29-17)
      - Questionnaires (Box 29)
        (29-18)
      - Ra-Re (Box 29)
        (29-19)
      - Radio (Box 29)
        (29-20)
      - Rf-Rn (Box 29)
        (29-21)
      - Ro-Rz (Box 29)
        (29-22)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 29)
        (29-23)
      - Sa-Sh (Box 29)
        (29-24)
      - Scholarships, Prizes, etc. (Box 29)
        (29-25)
      - Si-Sn (Box 29)
        (29-26)
      - Smith, Ira M. (Box 29)
        (29-27)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 29)
        (29-28)
      - So-Sz (Box 30)
        (30-1)
      - Stason, E. Blythe (Box 30)
        (30-2)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 30)
        (30-3)
      - T (Box 30)
        (30-4)
      - Ua-Uz (Box 30)
        (30-5)
      - U.S. Departments (Box 30)
        (30-6)
      - U.S. Legislature (Box 30)
        (30-7)
      - V (Box 30)
        (30-8)
      - Wa-We (Box 30)
        (30-9)
      - Wf-Wz (Box 30)
        (30-10)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 30)
        (30-11)
      - Yoakum, C.S. (Box 30)
        (30-12)
    - 1941-1942
      - Aa-Am (Box 30)
        (30-13)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 30)
        (30-14)
      - Alumni Association (Box 30)
        (30-15)
      - American (Box 30)
        (30-16)
      - American Council on Education (Box 30)
        (30-17)
      - An-Az (Box 30)
        (30-18)
      - Annuities (Box 30)
        (30-19)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 30)
        (30-20)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 30)
        (30-21)
      - Ba-Be (Box 30)
        (30-22)
      - Barbour Scholarships (Box 30)
        (30-23)
      - Bf-Bq (Box 30)
        (30-24)
      - Blakeman, Edward W. (Box 30)
        (30-25)
      - Br-Bz (Box 30)
        (30-26)
      - Burke, George J. (Box 30)
        (30-27)
      - Ca-Cd (Box 30)
        (30-28)
      - Ce-Ck (Box 30)
        (30-29)
      - Centennial Celebration (Box 30)
        (30-30)
      - Christensen, J.C. (Box 31)
        (31-1)
      - Cl-Co (Box 31)
        (31-2)
      - Clements Library (Box 31)
        (31-3)
      - Commencement (1942) (Box 31)
        (31-4)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 31)
        (31-5)
      - Da-Dn (Box 31)
        (31-6)
      - Do-Dz (Box 31)
        (31-7)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 31)
        (31-8)
      - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 31)
        (31-9)
      - Edmonson, J.B. (Box 31)
        (31-10)
      - Fa-Fq (Box 31)
        (31-11)
      - Fern, George H. (Box 31)
        (31-12)
      - Foreign Relations (Box 31)
        (31-13)
      - Fr-Fz (Box 31)
        (31-14)
      - Ga-Gn (Box 31)
        (31-15)
      - Go-Gz (Box 31)
        (31-16)
      - Griffin, Clare E. (Box 31)
        (31-17)
      - Ha-Hd (Box 31)
        (31-18)
      - He-Hz (Box 31)
        (31-19)
      - I (Box 31)
        (31-20)
      - J (Box 31)
        (31-21)
      - Ka-Kh (Box 31)
        (31-22)
      - Kellogg Foundation (Box 31)
        (31-23)
      - Ki-Kz (Box 31)
        (31-24)
      - La-Le (Box 31)
        (31-25)
      - Latin America (Box 31)
        (31-26)
      - Lf-Lz (Box 31)
        (31-27)
      - Ma-Mb (Box 31)
        (31-28)
      - Mc-Md (Box 31)
        (31-29)
      - Me-Mh (Box 31)
        (31-30)
      - Memberships (Box 31)
        (31-31)
      - Mi (Box 31)
        (31-32)
      - Michigan (Box 31)
        (31-33)
      - Nj-Mz (Box 32)
        (32-1)
      - Na-Nz (Box 32)
        (32-2)
      - National, etc. (Box 32)
        (32-3)
      - Naval R.O.T.C. (Box 32)
        (32-4)
      - Nelson, J. Raleigh (Box 32)
        (32-5)
      - O (Box 32)
        (32-6)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 32)
        (32-7)
      - Physical Education (Board in Control of) (Box 32)
        (32-8)
      - Questionnaires (Box 32)
        (32-9)
      - Ra-Re (Box 32)
        (32-10)
      - Rf-Rt (Box 32)
        (32-11)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 32)
        (32-12)
      - Ru-Rz (Box 32)
        (32-13)
      - Sa-Sd (Box 32)
        (32-14)
      - Scholarships, Prizes, etc. (Box 32)
        (32-15)
      - Se-Sn (Box 32)
        (32-16)
      - Shields, Edmund C. (Box 32)
        (32-17)
      - Smith (Miscellaneous) (Box 32)
        (32-18)
      - Smith, Ira M. (Box 32)
        (32-19)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 32)
        (32-20)
      - So-St (Box 32)
        (32-21)
      - Stason, E. Blythe (Box 32)
        (32-22)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 32)
        (32-23)
      - Student Religious Association (Box 32)
        (32-24)
      - Su-Sz (Box 32)
        (32-25)
      - Ta-Tg (Box 32)
        (32-26)
      - Tax Questions (Box 32)
        (32-27)
      - Th-Tz (Box 32)
        (32-28)
      - Twelve (Committee of) (Box 32)
        (32-29)
      - U (Box 32)
        (32-30)
      - V (Box 32)
        (32-31)
      - Wa-We (Box 32)
        (32-32)
      - Wf-Wz (Box 32)
        (32-33)
      - Williams, Robert (Box 32)
        (32-34)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 32)
        (32-35)
    - 1942-1943
      - Aa-Am (Box 33)
        (33-1)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 33)
        (33-2)
      - Alumni Association (Box 33)
        (33-3)
      - American (Box 33)
        (33-4)
      - American Council on Education (Box 33)
        (33-5)
      - An-Az (Box 33)
        (33-6)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 33)
        (33-7)
      - Associations, Bureaus, etc. (Box 33)
        (33-8)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 33)
        (33-9)
      - Associations (Meetings of) (Box 33)
        (33-10)
      - Ba-Bd (Box 33)
        (33-11)
      - Be-Bn (Box 33)
        (33-12)
      - Blakeman, Edward W. (Box 33)
        (33-13)
      - Bo-Br (Box 33)
        (33-14)
      - Bs-Bz (Box 33)
        (33-15)
      - Burke, George J. (Box 33)
        (33-16)
      - Ca-Cd (Box 33)
        (33-17)
      - Caldervood, Howard B. (Box 33)
        (33-18)
      - Ce-Cn (Box 33)
        (33-19)
      - Clements Library (Box 33)
        (33-20)
      - Co (Box 33)
        (33-21)
      - Commencement Talk Letters (Box 33)
        (33-22)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 33)
        (33-23)
      - Da-De (Box 33)
        (33-24)
      - Df-Dz (Box 33)
        (33-25)
      - Ea, Em (Box 33)
        (33-26)
      - Edmonson, J.B. (Box 33)
        (33-27)
      - En-Ez (Box 33)
        (33-28)
      - Fa-Fq (Box 33)
        (33-29)
      - Fern, George H. (Box 33)
        (33-30)
      - Foreign Relations (Box 33)
        (33-31)
      - Fr-Fz (Box 33)
        (33-32)
      - Furstenberg, Albert C. (Box 33)
        (33-33)
      - Ga-Go (Box 33)
        (33-34)
      - General Correspondence A-Z, 1942-1943 (Box 33)
        (33-35)
      - Governing Boards (Association of) (Box 33)
        (33-36)
      - Gp-Gz (Box 34)
        (34-1)
      - Ha-Hd (Box 34)
        (34-2)
      - Handicapped Children (Box 34)
        (34-3)
      - Haynes, Harley A. (Box 34)
        (34-4)
      - He-Hn (Box 34)
        (34-5)
      - Ho-Hz (Box 34)
        (34-6)
      - I-J (Box 34)
        (34-7)
      - Ka-Ke (Box 34)
        (34-8)
      - Kellogg Foundation (Box 34)
        (34-9)
      - Kf-Kz (Box 34)
        (34-10)
      - La-Le (Box 34)
        (34-11)
      - Latin America (Box 34)
        (34-12)
      - Lf-Lz (Box 34)
        (34-13)
      - Ma-Mb (Box 34)
        (34-14)
      - Me-Md (Box 34)
        (34-15)
      - Me-Mz (Box 34)
        (34-16)
      - Memberships (Box 34)
        (34-17)
      - Michigan (Box 34)
        (34-18)
      - Michigan Daily (Box 34)
        (34-19)
      - Na-Nz (Box 34)
        (34-20)
      - Naval R.O.T.C. (Box 34)
        (34-21)
      - Nelson, J. Raleigh (Box 34)
        (34-22)
      - Nelson, J.R. (Successor) (Box 34)
        (34-23)
      - North Central Association (Box 34)
        (34-24)
      - O (Box 34)
        (34-25)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 34)
        (34-26)
      - Physical Education (Board in Control of) (Box 34)
        (34-27)
      - Qa-Qz (Box 34)
        (34-28)
      - Questionnaires (Box 34)
        (34-29)
      - Ra-Ri (Box 34)
        (34-30)
      - Radio (Box 34)
        (34-31)
      - Rj-Rz (Box 34)
        (34-32)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 34)
        (34-33)
      - Sa-Sd (Box 35)
        (35-1)
      - Scholarships, Prizes, etc. (Box 35)
        (35-2)
      - Se-Sj (Box 35)
        (35-3)
      - Sk-Sp (Box 35)
        (35-4)
      - Smith (Miscellaneous) (Box 35)
        (35-5)
      - Smith, Ira. M. (Box 35)
        (35-6)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 35)
        (35-7)
      - Sq-Sz (Box 35)
        (35-8)
      - Stason, E. Blythe (Box 35)
        (35-9)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 35)
        (35-10)
      - Thirteen (Committee of) (Box 35)
        (35-11)
      - U (Box 35)
        (35-12)
      - Va-Vz (Box 35)
        (35-13)
      - Vaughan, Henry F. (Box 35)
        (35-14)
      - Wa-We (Box 35)
        (35-15)
      - Wf-Wz (Box 35)
        (35-16)
      - Williams, Robert (Box 35)
        (35-17)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 35)
        (35-18)
    - 1943-1944
      - Aa-Am (Box 35)
        (35-19)
      - Advisory Board on University Policies (Box 35)
        (35-20)
      - Alumni Association (Box 35)
        (35-21)
      - American (Box 35)
        (35-22)
      - American Council on Education (Box 35)
        (35-23)
      - An-Az (Box 35)
        (35-24)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 35)
        (35-25)
      - Associations, Bureaus, etc. (Box 35)
        (35-26)
      - Ba-Bd (Box 35)
        (35-27)
      - Barbour Scholarships (Box 35)
        (35-28)
      - Be-Bn (Box 35)
        (35-29)
      - Biographical Sketches (Box 35)
        (35-30)
      - Blakeman, Edward W. (Box 35)
        (35-31)
      - Bo-Br (Box 35)
        (35-32)
      - Bs-Bz (Box 35)
        (35-33)
      - Ca-Cd (Box 36)
        (36-1)
      - Ce-Co (Box 36)
        (36-2)
      - Civil Service (Box 36)
        (36-3)
      - Clements Library (Box 36)
        (36-4)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 36)
        (36-5)
      - Da-De (Box 36)
        (36-6)
      - Df-Dz (Box 36)
        (36-7)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 36)
        (36-8)
      - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 36)
        (36-9)
      - Fa-Fq (Box 36)
        (36-10)
      - Fern, George H (Box 36)
        (36-11)
      - Fr-Fz (Box 36)
        (36-12)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 36)
        (36-13)
      - Gale, Esson M (Box 36)
        (36-14)
      - Gram, L.M. (Box 36)
        (36-15)
      - Ha-Hd (Box 36)
        (36-16)
      - Haynes, Harley H (Box 36)
        (36-17)
      - Hayward, Ralph A (Box 36)
        (36-18)
      - He-Hi (Box 36)
        (36-19)
      - Hj-Hz (Box 36)
        (36-20)
      - Ia-Iz (Box 36)
        (36-21)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics (Board in Control of) (Box 36)
        (36-22)
      - J (Box 36)
        (36-23)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 36)
        (36-24)
      - Kelly, Harry F. (Box 36)
        (36-25)
      - Kraus, Edward H. (Box 36)
        (36-26)
      - La-Lh (Box 36)
        (36-27)
      - Labor (Box 36)
        (36-28)
      - Latin-American Bulletin (Box 36)
        (36-29)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 36)
        (36-30)
      - Li-Lz (Box 36)
        (36-31)
      - Ma-Md (Box 36)
        (36-32)
      - Marckwardt, Albert H. (Box 36)
        (36-33)
      - McClusky, Howard Y. (Box 36)
        (36-34)
      - Me-Mi (Box 36)
        (36-35)
      - Memberships (Box 36)
        (36-36)
      - Michigan (Box 36)
        (36-37)
      - Mj-Mz (Box 36)
        (36-38)
      - Na-Ne (Box 37)
        (37-1)
      - Nf-Nz (Box 37)
        (37-2)
      - Nurses (Box 37)
        (37-3)
      - O (Box 37)
        (37-4)
      - Pa-Pi (Box 37)
        (37-5)
      - Pj-Pz (Box 37)
        (37-6)
      - Qa-Qz (Box 37)
        (37-7)
      - Questionnaires (Box 37)
        (37-8)
      - Ra-Ri (Box 37)
        (37-9)
      - Radio (WJR) (Box 37)
        (37-10)
      - Redding, Rhoda (Box 37)
        (37-11)
      - Rj-Rz (Box 37)
        (37-12)
      - Rural Education (Box 37)
        (37-13)
      - Sa-Sh (Box 37)
        (37-14)
      - Scholarships, Prizes, etc. (Box 37)
        (37-15)
      - Si-Sz (Box 37)
        (37-16)
      - Smith (Miscellaneous) (Box 37)
        (37-17)
      - Smith, Ira M. (Box 37)
        (37-18)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 37)
        (37-19)
      - Stason, E. Blythe (Box 37)
        (37-20)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 37)
        (37-21)
      - Thirteen (Committee of) (Box 37)
        (37-22)
      - Towe, Larry (Box 37)
        (37-23)
      - U (Box 37)
        (37-24)
      - Va-Vz (Box 37)
        (37-25)
      - Visitors (Box 37)
        (37-26)
      - Wa-Wh (Box 37)
        (37-27)
      - Wi-Wz (Box 37)
        (37-28)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 37)
        (37-29)
      - Yoakum, C.S. (Box 37)
        (37-30)
      - Zimmerman (Latin America) (Box 37)
        (37-31)
    - 1944-1945
      - Aa-Az (Box 37)
        (37-32)
      - Adams, James F. (Box 37)
        (37-33)
      - Advisory Board on University Policies (Box 37)
        (37-34)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 37)
        (37-35)